let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What is the port number for HTTP ?",
        answer: "80",
        options: [
            "80",
            "81",
            "82",
            "79"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What is the port number for HTTPS ?",
        answer: "443",
        options: [
            "240",
            "340",
            "443",
            "540"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "What is the port number for RDP ?",
        answer: "3389",
        options: [
            "3389",
            "3380",
            "2800",
            "3500"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What is the port number for DNS?",
        answer: "53",
        options: [
            "50",
            "51",
            "52",
            "53"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What is the port number for SSH ?",
        answer: "22",
        options: [
            "22",
            "21",
            "20",
            "23"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "What is the port number for SMB ?",
        answer: "445",
        options: [
            "345",
            "441",
            "445",
            "444"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "What is the port number for TELNET ?",
        answer: "23",
        options: [
            "27",
            "26",
            "23",
            "28"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "What is the port number for POP3 ?",
        answer: "110",
        options: [
            "110",
            "98",
            "80",
            "95"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "What is the port number for IMAP ?",
        answer: "143",
        options: [
            "120",
            "143",
            "122",
            "150"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "What is the port number for SMTP",
        answer: "25",
        options: [
            "31",
            "30",
            "25",
            "32"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "What is the port number for FTP",
        answer: "21",
        options: [
            "21",
            "35",
            "28",
            "42"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "What is the port number for SFTP",
        answer: "22",
        options: [
            "35",
            "34",
            "22",
            "39"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "What is the port number for DHCP",
        answer: "68",
        options: [
            "68",
            "80",
            "85",
            "90"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "What is the port number for TFTP",
        answer: "69",
        options: [
            "71",
            "69",
            "75",
            "82"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "What is the port number for NTP",
        answer: "123",
        options: [
            "123",
            "100",
            "125",
            "132"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "What is the port number for IMAP4",
        answer: "143",
        options: [
            "131",
            "143",
            "215",
            "321"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "What is the port number for SNMP",
        answer: "161",
        options: [
            "331",
            "330",
            "161",
            "302"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "What is the port number for LDAP",
        answer: "389",
        options: [
            "311",
            "3023",
            "235",
            "389"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "What is the port number for LDAPS",
        answer: "636",
        options: [
            "319",
            "303",
            "653",
            "636"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "What is the port number for H.323",
        answer: "1720",
        options: [
            "3132",
            "3034",
            "1720",
            "3233"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 21,
        question: "What is the port number for SIP",
        answer: "5060",
        options: [
            "5063",
            "5060",
            "4023",
            "5054"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 22,
        question: "What is the port number for FTP-DATA",
        answer: "20",
        options: [
            "24",
            "26",
            "20",
            "12"
        ]
    },

]